{
  "name": "Spanish 100",
  "editable": false,
  "data": [
    {
      "front": "semana",
      "back": "week"
    },
    {
      "front": "año",
      "back": "year"
    },
    {
      "front": "hoy",
      "back": "today"
    },
    {
      "front": "mañana",
      "back": "tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "front": "ayer",
      "back": "yesterday"
    },
    {
      "front": "calendario",
      "back": "calendar"
    },
    {
      "front": "segundo",
      "back": "second"
    },
    {
      "front": "hora",
      "back": "hour"
    },
    {
      "front": "minuto",
      "back": "minute"
    },
    {
      "front": "en punto",
      "back": "o'clock"
    },
    {
      "front": "reloj",
      "back": "clock"
    },
    {
      "front": "poder",
      "back": "can"
    },
    {
      "front": "usar",
      "back": "use"
    },
    {
      "front": "hacer",
      "back": "do"
    },
    {
      "front": "ir",
      "back": "go"
    },
    {
      "front": "venir",
      "back": "come"
    },
    {
      "front": "reírse",
      "back": "laugh"
    },
    {
      "front": "hacer",
      "back": "make"
    },
    {
      "front": "ver",
      "back": "see"
    },
    {
      "front": "lejos",
      "back": "far"
    },
    {
      "front": "pequeño",
      "back": "small"
    },
    {
      "front": "bueno",
      "back": "good"
    },
    {
      "front": "hermoso",
      "back": "beautiful"
    },
    {
      "front": "feo",
      "back": "ugly"
    },
    {
      "front": "difícil",
      "back": "difficult"
    },
    {
      "front": "fácil",
      "back": "easy"
    },
    {
      "front": "malo",
      "back": "bad"
    },
    {
      "front": "cerca",
      "back": "near"
    },
    {
      "front": "Encantado de conocerte.",
      "back": "Nice to meet you"
    },
    {
      "front": "Hola.",
      "back": "Hello."
    },
    {
      "front": "Buenos días.",
      "back": "Good morning."
    },
    {
      "front": "Buenas tardes.",
      "back": "Good afternoon."
    },
    {
      "front": "Buenas noches.",
      "back": "Good night"
    },
    {
      "front": "¿Cómo estás?",
      "back": "How are you?"
    },
    {
      "front": "Gracias.",
      "back": "Thank you!"
    },
    {
      "front": "No.",
      "back": "No."
    },
    {
      "front": "¡Delicioso!",
      "back": "Delicious!"
    },
    {
      "front": "Soy... (nombre)",
      "back": "I'm...(name)."
    },
    {
      "front": "Adiós.",
      "back": "Goodbye."
    },
    {
      "front": "Sí.",
      "back": "Yes."
    },
    {
      "front": "lunes",
      "back": "Monday"
    },
    {
      "front": "martes",
      "back": "Tuesday"
    },
    {
      "front": "miércoles",
      "back": "Wednesday"
    },
    {
      "front": "jueves",
      "back": "Thursday"
    },
    {
      "front": "viernes",
      "back": "Friday"
    },
    {
      "front": "sábado",
      "back": "Saturday"
    },
    {
      "front": "domingo",
      "back": "Sunday"
    },
    {
      "front": "mayo",
      "back": "May"
    },
    {
      "front": "enero",
      "back": "January"
    },
    {
      "front": "febrero",
      "back": "February"
    },
    {
      "front": "marzo",
      "back": "March"
    },
    {
      "front": "abril",
      "back": "April"
    },
    {
      "front": "junio",
      "back": "June"
    },
    {
      "front": "julio",
      "back": "July"
    },
    {
      "front": "agosto",
      "back": "August"
    },
    {
      "front": "septiembre",
      "back": "September"
    },
    {
      "front": "octubre",
      "back": "October"
    },
    {
      "front": "noviembre",
      "back": "November"
    },
    {
      "front": "diciembre",
      "back": "December"
    },
    {
      "front": "cero",
      "back": "zero"
    },
    {
      "front": "uno",
      "back": "one"
    },
    {
      "front": "dos",
      "back": "two"
    },
    {
      "front": "tres",
      "back": "three"
    },
    {
      "front": "cuatro",
      "back": "four"
    },
    {
      "front": "cinco",
      "back": "five"
    },
    {
      "front": "seis",
      "back": "six"
    },
    {
      "front": "siete",
      "back": "seven"
    },
    {
      "front": "ocho",
      "back": "eight"
    },
    {
      "front": "nueve",
      "back": "nine"
    },
    {
      "front": "diez",
      "back": "ten"
    },
    {
      "front": "café",
      "back": "coffee"
    },
    {
      "front": "cerveza",
      "back": "beer"
    },
    {
      "front": "té",
      "back": "tea"
    },
    {
      "front": "vino",
      "back": "wine"
    },
    {
      "front": "agua",
      "back": "water"
    },
    {
      "front": "ternera",
      "back": "beef"
    },
    {
      "front": "carne de cerdo",
      "back": "pork"
    },
    {
      "front": "pollo",
      "back": "chicken"
    },
    {
      "front": "cordero",
      "back": "lamb"
    },
    {
      "front": "pescado",
      "back": "fish"
    },
    {
      "front": "pie",
      "back": "foot"
    },
    {
      "front": "pierna",
      "back": "leg"
    },
    {
      "front": "cabeza",
      "back": "head"
    },
    {
      "front": "brazo",
      "back": "arm"
    },
    {
      "front": "mano",
      "back": "hand"
    },
    {
      "front": "dedo",
      "back": "finger"
    },
    {
      "front": "cuerpo",
      "back": "body"
    },
    {
      "front": "estómago",
      "back": "stomach"
    },
    {
      "front": "espalda",
      "back": "back"
    },
    {
      "front": "pecho",
      "back": "chest"
    },
    {
      "front": "enfermera",
      "back": "nurse"
    },
    {
      "front": "empleado",
      "back": "employee"
    },
    {
      "front": "oficial de policía",
      "back": "police officer"
    },
    {
      "front": "cocinero",
      "back": "cook"
    },
    {
      "front": "ingeniero",
      "back": "engineer"
    },
    {
      "front": "médico",
      "back": "doctor"
    },
    {
      "front": "encargado",
      "back": "manager"
    },
    {
      "front": "profesora",
      "back": "teacher"
    },
    {
      "front": "programador",
      "back": "programmer"
    },
    {
      "front": "vendedor",
      "back": "salesman"
    }
  ]
}
